地球人
欢迎关注微博@ UUU字幕组 获取最新熟肉信息!
UUU字幕组
翻译
右翼部鸣明/ 草
校对
Husky/ 牙牙
特效
presisco
出品
压制
presisco/ 依依
铁石英!
Jasper!
她在干嘛呢?
What is she doing?
她最近一直在收集宝石怪物
She's been collecting monsters.
安静!
Pipe down!
你们现在开始要服从我的命令!
You take orders from me now!
你曾经也是颗石英 不是吗?
You used to be a quartz, too, didn't you?
在你身上发生了什么?
What happened to you?
呃! 肮脏
Ugh! Disgraceful.
不敢相信我居然收下你这种怪物做手下!
I can't believe I've resorted to recruiting you freaks!
你和水晶战士中的那个矮子一样糟糕
You're almost as bad as that crystal runt.
瞧瞧你
Just look at you.
这个星球毁掉了一切
This planet ruins everything.
好吧 除了我
Well except for me.
我们应该回神庙里叫上其他人
We should go back to the temple and grab reinforcements.
对 这是个好主意
Yeah, that's a good idea.
紫晶?
Amethyst?
紫晶!
Amethyst!
我永远不会让这颗星球像扭曲你这样毁掉我
I'll never let this planet twist me like it twisted you.
你的脆弱让母星蒙羞
Your weakness embarrasses Homeworld.
你的痛苦都是你自找的
You suffer because it's what you deserve.
我们身上发生的都理所应当
We all only get what we deserve.
对不对 紫晶?
Right, Amethyst?
哈?
Huh?
你来这里做什么 矮子?
What do you want, runt?
你要再次挑战我?
You here for a rematch?
我是来打败你的!
I'm here to win!
你出场的瞬间 已经注定会输了
You were fated to lose--the moment you came out wrong.
你胡说!
That's not true!
玫瑰 果不其然
Rose. Of course.
你的走狗在你也不会太远的
Your lackeys never stray far.
当然他们也不会离开你的
And why would they?
因为其他任何地方他们都没有立足之处了!
They have no place in this or any world!
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
每个宝石都是为了某种目的而制造出的--
Every gem is made for a purpose--
为了服侍钻石的圣旨
to serve the order of the diamonds.
那些无法完成钻石命令的必须被清除!
Those who cannot fit inside this order must be purged!
出生时畸形的体态
To come out misshapen,
按照自己意愿胡乱变形
to reshape yourself outside your purpose,
保护这个无药可救 没用的星球
and to defend this ruined, worthless planet
这些都是耻辱!
is a disgrace!
这颗星球也没那么糟
This planet isn't all bad.
你在这儿干嘛呢?
What are you doing here?
我...
I...
我现在也是个水晶战士了!
I'm a crystal gem now!
我不怕你!
I'm not afraid of you!
我现在有金属能力了!
I've got metal powers!
你瞧着吧!
I'll show you!
啊啊老天
Aw, geez.
等等
In a moment.
还有人有要说的吗?
Anyone else got something to say?
不! 没有别人了
No! It's just us.
呃! 你们!
Ugh! You guys!
-哈?!-别来凑热闹了!
-Huh?!-Stay out of this!
紫晶!
Amethyst!
这是咱俩间的事 铁石英--
It's just you and me, Jasper--
一对一!
one on one!
上 紫晶!
Go, Amethyst!
现在谁是矮子了?
Who's the runt now?
你准备好了?
You ready for more?
还--还有别的招数呢
Th--There's more where that came from.
啊哦
-Uh-oh.
哈?
Huh?
结束了吗?
Is it sinking in yet?
你是认真的吗?!
Are you serious?!
紫晶!
Amethyst!
你从未有过机会
You never had a chance.
抬头!
Heads up!
-哈?-哈?
-Huh?-Huh?
史蒂文 我赢不了
Steven I can't win.
无论我做什么 无论我多么努力
No matter what I do, no matter how hard I work,
她生来完美 我生来卑微
she came out right, and I came out wrong.
这是铁石英认为的
That's just what Jasper thinks.
只有她觉得你本应该像她一样
She's the only one who thinks you should be like her.
-但是-不要再试图变得和铁石英一样了
-But-Stop trying to be like Jasper.
你和铁石英完全不同!
You're nothing like Jasper!
你更像我--
You're like me--
因为我们都是这样格格不入
because we're both not like anybody!
是啊 这是挺糟糕的
And, yeah, it sucks.
但至少我还有你
But at least I've got you.
你也有我
And you've got me.
所以不要再抛下我一个人战斗了
So stop leaving me out of this.
最糟的宝石总得呆在一起不是吗?
Us worst gems stick together right?
这也是为什么我们是最棒的
That's why we're the best.
多么美好的一天!
What a beautiful day! w
哈? 你是谁?
Huh?! Who are you supposed to be?
哦对啊 我现在是谁来着?
Oh, yeah! Who am I now?
我想紫晶应该知道我是谁
I feel like Amethyst knows this.
先别管你的名字了--你还有一场架要干呢
Forget your name--you've got a fight to win!
我想一个玫瑰石英和一个紫水晶
I think a rose quartz and an amethyst...
在一起就是
...make a...
烟晶
...Smoky Quartz.
你们水晶宝石难道现在只懂融合这招吗
Is fusion the only trick you crystal gems know?
嘛我懂的招式还真不少
I've got plenty of tricks.
见过 [ 前抛] 没有
Ever see sink the dink?
不
No!
我的军队
My army!
哈糊你一脸
Take that!
再吃我这招
Then take this!
啊 这么快就要离开啦
Aw. Leaving so soon?
我不会再败在融合上了
I will not be beaten by another fusion!
什么鬼
What the...
铁石英的融合体与"辐射"系列中的死亡爪相似
等等
Hold on.
我还真有个可以把你干飞的招
I've got a move that will really blow you away.
你不喜欢也没关系
It's cool if you don't like it.
我已经准备了三个大风扇啦
I've already got three huge fans.
我们只要坚持在一起...就可以打败她们
We could beat them...if we stay together.
干的漂亮 小烟
Great job, Smoky.
噢 谢谢 谢了 小烟
Oh, thank you, thank you, Smoky.
跟我融合的人从来没有愿意留下的
Nobody I fuse with ever wants to stay.
噫 超恶心啦
Ew! That's disgusting.
是堕转
It's corruption.
史蒂文 小心啊
Steven, be careful.
但是我不能眼睁睁地看着它发生
But this just happened.
也许我可以做些什么
Maybe I can do something.
铁石英 没事的
Jasper, it's okay.
我就在这里
I'm here.
玫瑰
Rose.
我不是玫瑰 我是史蒂文
I'm not Rose. I'm Steven.
我现在只想试着治愈你
I just want to try and heal you.
史蒂文
Steven!
什么 别冲动
What? Stop.
我现在知道你的把戏了
I see how you do it now, Rose.
你在宝石人失去价值后再去收她们入伙
You want gems after they're worthless.
你一直等到她们失败才动手
You wait until after they've lost.
因为当你到了最倒霉的时候
Because when you're at the bottom,
就会顺从于从任何人
you'll follow anyone.
这会减轻你的挫败感
That makes you feel like less of a failure.
呃 就看看这个家伙
Ugh. Just look at this one.
你剥夺了她的一切--
You've stripped her of everything--
她的扩增肢 她的地位 她的尊严
her limb enhancers, her status, her dignity.
我还有一样呢
I still have one of those things.
你怎么可以站在玫瑰石英那边
How can you side with Rose Quartz?
为什么
Why?
为什么要保护这个没用的空壳行星
Why protect this useless shell of a planet?
它不是一个空壳
It's not a shell.
这里还有数不胜数的生命
There's so much life.
生活--这就是我在这里做的事啊
Living here--that's what I'm doing!
我生活在这里
I'm living here.
现在我每时每刻都在了解自己未发掘的潜能
I've been learning new things about myself all the time,
比如现在我可以让金属都顺从我的旨意
like how I can make metal do my bidding.
重点是...
The point being...
地球可以给你自由
Earth can set you free.
地球...就是一个监牢
Earth...is a prison.
我之所以可以离开是因为我远远优于这个鬼地方
I got out because I'm better than this place.
情况在恶化
It's getting worse.
我回来就是为了结果你们
I only came back to finish you off.
尽量不要动
Try not to move.
你休想操控我 玫瑰石英
You can't manipulate me, Rose Quartz.
我-我不是想操控你
I-I'm not manipulating.
我只是想帮忙
I'm--I'm trying to help.
帮忙
Help?
Help?!
自我从这地壳破土而出
I've been fighting
我就一直在战斗
from the second I broke free of the Earth's crust
只因你对我的殖民地做的事
because of what you did to my colony,
只因你对我的星球所做的事
because of what you did to my planet,
只因你对我的钻石所做的事
because of what you did to my diamond!
我--你说黄钻?
I--Yellow Diamond?
我的钻石!
My diamond!
你的钻石!
Your diamond!
粉红钻石!
Pink diamond!
不用谢哈
You're welcome.
来吧 老姐
Come here, sis.
当我们回到谷仓后
When we get to the barn,
我要做个巨型金属溜溜球
I'm building a giant metal yo-yo.
紫晶 史蒂文 到时候你们要给我用它玩玩抛接
Amethyst, Steven, you'll have to catch and throw it for me.
接下来的 大概一个月 我都不想做任何事了
I don't want to do anything for, like, a month.